(Penny:)See, that's where you come in.
I'll start over.
(Sheldon(singing):)Soft kitty, warm kitty
Little ball of fur
(Penny:)I've got all night, Sheldon.
(Sheldon(singing):)Soft kitty, warm kitty
(Sheldon(singing):)-Little ball of fur
-Soft kitty, warm kitty
-Happy kitty, sleepy kitty
(Penny:)-Happy kitty, sleepy kitty
-Purr, purr, purr
(Penny:)Purr, purr, purr
(Raj:)And the next morning when he woke up,
he rolled over and realized--
Da, da, da!
(Raj:)--she was his cousin.
[LEONARD & RAJESH LAUGHING]
(Howard:)That's still not funny.
[IMITATING HOWARD]
"That's still not funny."
(Howard:)And she was my second cousin.
"And she was my second cousin."
(Howard:)You're a real douche.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Who cares? You slept with your cousin.